在ForecaseFragment类中，我们修改了
In the ForecaseFragment class, we modify the
onOptionsItemSelected()方法。当点击Refresh按钮时，
onOptionsItemSelected method. When the Refresh menu item is selected,
我们创建了一个新的FetchWeatherTask对象，并且我们调用
we create a new FetchWeatherTask and then we call
它的execute()方法。尽管由于使用的是AsyncTask
execute on it. While the call is no longer
调用并不会阻塞UI线程，
blocking the UI thread because it's an AsyncTask, the
但是应用仍然会崩溃。如果你查看日志，
app will still crash. If we check the logs,
我们会看到应用这一次是由于一个SecurityException（安全异常）
we see that the app crashed, this time though,
崩溃的。它说权限被拒绝，并且问
with a SecurityException. It says Permission denied and
是不是没有申请INTERNET权限。确实，
ask if you're missing the INTERNET permission or not. And indeed,
我们没申请INTERNET权限，因此我们需要申请它。
we are missing the INTERNET permission, so we need to request it.